marshall.edu 2008-12-17

# Marshall University Privacy Policy

**  
Marshall University Privacy Policy  
**_Last Updated: January 7, 2003_

**Notice: The following statement represents the information collection and use practices of the official Marshall University website,www.marshall.edu. The Marshall University website links to other sites within the marshall.edu domain and various other external sites which are not covered by this policy.**

Thank you for visiting the Marshall University website. We understand your concerns regarding privacy and make no attempt to collect personal information of any kind unless you choose to make such information available.

When you visit the Marshall University website, our web server automatically logs the domain, IP address and software (browser and platform) by which you accessed the website. This information does not identify your name, username, email address or other personal information.

Additional information is collected by our web server such as the date, time and volume of web page accesses. We collect and review this information in order to evaluate the effectiveness of Marshall University's web presence and to improve the experience of visitors to the website. Again, this information is non-personal, and is not sold or provided to other organizations.

Should you make the choice to submit personal information to us by sending an email or filling out an electronic form, we will use the information only for purposes which you have given authorization. This information may be stored for a period of time by the university organizations for which it was collected, but it will not be disclosed to outside organizations or government agencies unless the disclosure is required by state or federal law. In the event of such a disclosure, we will do our best to notify you in advance.

If you have any questions regarding privacy or the practices of the Marshall University website, please contact the Marshall University Webmaster - [ webmaster@marshall.edu](mailto:webmaster@marshall.edu).
